Most often, the teacher has adapted the group so that you get good dynamics.
Much of the oral national are things you already can-
-for example.
To talk, listen and answer questions.
Under National you should do just that - just with a little more commitment.
Before English, plug in synonyms!
You get a larger vocabulary and can use more advanced formulations.
Practice discussions with people in your vicinity.
Listen and ask questions.
The stress before the test may feel hard, but it can help us!
In case of short-term stress, adrenaline is excreted, making us alert-
-And it makes us think and reason faster.
Visualize that the test is going well.